Austin Baxley

¶ Atlanta, Georgia, United States
¶ AusBaxley@gmail.com
¶ 678-435-3558
¶ in/abaxley2
¶ https://github.com/abaxley2

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, maintaining, and building websites and web applications. Demonstrates leadership in fast-paced goal-oriented environments. Specializes in JavaScript and have experience with using MySQL, NoSQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars, and React.

PROJECTS

Regex Tutorial

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp • August 2021

- Developed a working tutorial on Regular Expressions that resulted in an A.
- Explained in detail each aspect of Regex and it's applicable use.
- Successfully deployed a GitHub Gist.
- GitHub Gist: https://gist.github.com/abaxley2/a796040212cdac792dc67c286ba42a41

Market Finder

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp • June 2021

- Created a web application that used third party APIs to locate local farmer's markets by location.
- Wrote and managed project assignments.
- Successfully deployed the application through GitHub resulting in an A.
- Technologies Used: ¡Query, Tailwind CSS.
- GitHub Link: https://github.com/abaxley2/Market-Finder
- Deployed Link: https://abaxley2.github.io/Market-Finder/

EXPERIENCE

Restaurant Manager

Tin Lizzy's Cantina

January 2020 - April 2023, Atlanta, GA

- Launched new product offerings resulting in a 15% sales revenue increase
- Managed inventory and reduced costs by 9%.
- Led diverse team with efficient scheduling, increasing sales by 5% year over year and reducing staff turnover by 30%.

Band Director

Cobb County Schools

September 2013 - May 2016, Marietta, GA

- Developed curriculum and conducted clinics to enable students to learn in an adaptable setting.
- Performed and organized at over 40 performances including concerts, festivals, and parades.
- Instructed and maintained a group of over 400 students each year.

Restaurant Manager

CentraArchy Restaurant Management Group

March 2013 - December 2019, Atlanta, GA

- Sourced, developed, and trained new restaurant managers.
- Increased key metrics including guest counts, revenue per guest.
- Increased overall revenue by 15%.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Music in Music Education

Kennesaw State University • Kennesaw, GA • 2012

Professional Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

Georgia Institute of Technology • Atlanta, GA • 2021

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Express, Mongoose, Graphql Apollo, MVC, Mongo Db, NoSQL, MySQL